Dauren Yesselbayev

Golang Junior Developer

Kazakhstan, Astana | +7 (705) 904 49 00 | yesselbayev.d@gmail.com

https://github.com/dyesselb | https://www.linkedin.com/in/dyesselbayev

Profile

Enthusiastic Golang developer with skills in development to implement theoretical knowledge in enterprise level implementation. I had many hurdles and had to adapt quickly but I enjoy learning new skills and thrive when being challenged. My experience at Alem School helped me develop the basic skills of Golang language and some advanced topics as well.

I want to continue making contributions and improving as a developer.

Education

Alem School | Kazakhstan, Astana | 01.09.2022 - ...

· Golang, JavaScript, Rust

Tomsk Polytechnic University | Tomsk, Russian Federation | 2019

· BACHELOR OF APPLIED GEOLOGY

Skills

PRIMARY

Golang (junior), SQL (basic), Git(basic), Bash(middle)

SECONDARY

HTML5, CSS, CMS WordPress, Adobe PS, Ill

Work Experience

Exploration Geologist | "Nordgold" PLC | 03.2021 - 07.2022

· Geological services and control of drilling

Mud logger Analyst | Schlumberger Logelco Inc | 12.2017-06.2020

- · Well control and monitoring
- · Geological description of the well during all stages of drilling

Junior Geologist | "Geotek" LLP | 06.2013-02.2017

· Geological maintain for mining and drilling operations

Languages

Kazakh (native), Russian (Proficiency), English (Intermediate)

Certificates

GN5 Acquisition Course

Schlumberger Middle East & Asia Learning Center 2019 UAE, Abu Dhabi

MLA-1 Course

Schlumberger Middle East & Asia Learning Center 2018 UAE, Abu Dhabi